[Music]
[音乐]
this is nick with logos by nick.com and
这是尼克和Nick.com的徽标
in this tutorial i'll be demonstrating
在本教程中，我将演示
how you can use
如何使用
inkscape for desktop publishing purposes
用于桌面出版目的的Inkscape
to create things like reports
创建类似于报告的东西
manuals ebooks and various other types
手册、电子书和各种其他类型
of pdf documents
Pdf文档的
now granted inkscape probably isn't the
现在承认Inkscape可能不是
best tool for this sort of thing
解决这类问题的最佳工具
but if you just need to create a simple
但如果您只需要创建一个简单的
one or two page document
一页或两页文档
or maybe even a short ebook and you're
或者甚至是一本短小的电子书，你会
already somewhat familiar with inkscape
对Inkscape已经有些熟悉了
then it would probably be more practical
那么它可能会更实用
than taking the time to learn
而不是花时间学习
an entirely new piece of software like
一款全新的软件，如
scribus or indesign
Scribus或InDesign
i've used inkscape myself to create
我自己用Inkscape创作了
manuals and ebooks in the past so i know
过去的手册和电子书，所以我知道
that it's perfectly capable in that
它完全有能力做到这一点
regard
关照
before we get started though if you'd
在我们开始之前，如果你愿意
like to learn everything that there is
想要了解那里的一切
to know about inkscape
了解Inkscape
be sure to check out my inkscape master
一定要看看我的Inkscape大师
class it's a collection of over 60
班级它是一个超过60个人的集合
videos where i go over
我看过的视频
every tool and feature in inkscape and i
Inkscape和我的每一个工具和功能
explain what it is and demonstrate how
解释它是什么，并演示它如何
it works
它起作用了
i'll have a link in the description of
我会在描述中有一个链接
the video if you want to check that out
这个视频如果你想看看的话
so to get us started here in inkscape
为了让我们从Inkscape开始
i'm going to open up a new document and
我要打开一份新文档，
then set up the documents that we are
然后设置我们正在使用的文档
all working with a similar workflow
都使用类似的工作流程
come up here to where it says view make
到这里来，上面写着要看风景
sure we have custom selected
当然，我们已经选择了定制
and then come up to zoom and go to zoom
然后上前进行缩放，然后转到缩放
in at one to one
以1比1的比分进入
and then we'll open up the align and
然后我们将打开Align和
distribute menu with this button right
向右按此按钮的分发菜单
here
这里
and then open up the fill and stroke
然后打开填充和描边
menu with this button right here
这里有这个按钮的菜单
and over here where it says snapping we
在这里，上面写着我们在抓拍
want to make sure we have enable
我想确保我们已启用
snapping enabled
已启用捕捉
and we want this one enabled right here
我们希望在这里启用这一功能
that says snap nodes
这表示捕捉节点
pads and handles we also want this one
垫子和手柄我们也想要这个
enabled that says snap to cusp nodes
已启用捕捉到尖点节点的选项
including rectangle corners
包括矩形拐角
and the one next to it as well snap to
而它旁边的那一张也是
smoothnose we're going to enable that
我们将启用这一功能
and then over here where it says snap
然后在这里，上面写着抓拍
text anchors and baselines
文本锚点和基线
enable that and then finally over here
启用它，然后最后在这里
where it says snap to the page border
其中显示靠齐页面边框
enable that as well
也启用该功能
and also you're going to want to make
而且你还会想要让
sure you have snap guides enabled as
确保已启用捕捉辅助线作为
well
井
but that should be enabled by default
但这应该在默认情况下启用
but if it's not go ahead and enable that
但如果它不继续并使之成为可能
so what i want to do now is set up the
所以我现在要做的是设置
canvas so that it's suitable for
画布，以便它适合于
creating these
正在创建这些
pdf documents we're going to create so
我们要创建的PDF文档
we'll come over here to where it says
我们会到这里来，上面写着
file
文件
click on document properties
单击文档属性
then where it says display units i want
然后它会显示我想要的显示单位
to change that to inches
要把它改成英寸
and over here where it says page size we
在这里，它显示我们的页面大小
have a list of templates here i'm going
我在这里有一个模板列表，我要去
to choose us
选择我们
letter which is 8.5 by 11 inches if you
大小为8.5 x 11英寸的字母
want to create something like an a5 or
想要创建类似a5或
an a1 or maybe even us legal you can use
A1，甚至是我们的法律，你可以使用
that if you want for this tutorial i'm
如果你想学习这篇教程，我是
just going to do the standard 8.5 by 11
只是要在11年前完成标准的8.5
inches
英寸
over here where it says border we want
在这里，上面写着我们想要的边界
to leave show page border enabled
使显示页面边框处于启用状态
border on top of drawing we're going to
画图上的边框，我们将
enable that that should be helpful when
在以下情况下启用应该会有帮助的
we're creating our design
我们正在创造我们的设计
and then show border shadow let's just
然后显示边框阴影让我们
disable that
禁用该功能
and then finally over here where it says
然后最后在这里，上面写着
background color i'm going to change
我要更改背景颜色
this
这
i'm going to click on the hsl tab and
我将单击HSL选项卡，然后
i'm going to come down here to the l row
我要到L这一排来
and slide this to the left a little bit
把这个滑到左边一点
if you notice the canvas
如果你注意到画布
is becoming darker as i do that and we
当我这样做的时候，我们变得越来越黑暗
want the canvas to be slightly darker
我想让画布稍微暗一点
than white because
而不是白色，因为
white is going to be the color of the
白色将会成为
page we create here
我们在此处创建的页面
so let me close out of that we should be
所以让我来结束我们应该做的
all set now close out of that
现在一切都结束了
what i want to do now is create a
我现在想做的是创建一个
rectangle to place in this page border
放置在此页面边框中的矩形
here is going to represent the white
这里代表的是白人
page of the document so i'll grab the
文档的页面，因此我将获取
squares and rectangles tool
正方形和矩形工具
and i'll snap to the top left corner of
我将捕捉到左上角的
the page click and drag and then snap to
页面点击并拖动，然后对齐到
the bottom right corner of the page to
页面的右下角
create this rectangle there
在那里创建这个矩形
and i want to make this rectangle white
我想把这个长方形变成白色
make sure your opacity is all the way up
确保您的不透明度一直向上
at 100
在100岁
and make sure you don't have an outline
确保你没有一个提纲
around your object otherwise known as a
围绕您的对象，也称为
stroke if you do have a stroke added to
笔划，如果您确实已将笔划添加到
your object just hold
您的对象只需保持
shift and click this red x down here to
按住Shift键并单击此处的红色x即可
get rid of it
把它扔掉
and then finally up here where it says
最后在这里，上面写着
make shoulders make corners sharp we
让肩膀变得锋利我们让角落变得尖锐
want to make sure we have sharp corners
想要确保我们有锋利的角落
while we're doing this so if this is not
当我们这样做的时候，如果这不是
grayed out go ahead and click on that
显示为灰色，请继续并单击该选项
we don't want our page to have rounded
我们不希望我们的页面有四舍五入
corners
转角
okay so now that we have our page set we
好的，现在我们已经设置了页面，现在
need to define the content
需要定义内容
area of this page we don't want the
此页的区域，我们不希望
content to run all the way to the edges
满足于一路跑到边缘
here so we want to create one inch of
在这里，我们要创建一英寸的
padding going around the document here
在此处填充文档
so to do that let me grab the select
因此，要做到这一点，让我拿起精选
tool let me right click on this
工具让我在上面右击
dot this rectangle here and go to
在这里画上这个矩形，然后转到
duplicate and i'm just going to make
复制品，我要做的就是
this red so we can differentiate it this
这是红色的，所以我们可以用这个来区分它
is just temporarily
只是暂时的
and up here where it says width and
上面写着宽度和
height or w and h
高度或宽和高
we're going to remove an inch from each
我们要把每一块都去掉一英寸
dimension so it's going to be 7.5 by 11.
所以它将是7.5乘以11。
before we do this though make sure you
在我们这么做之前，请确保你
don't have this lock icon enabled make
请不要启用此锁定图标
sure it's disabled like i have it here
当然，它是禁用的，就像我这里有的一样
so i'm going to change this to 7.5
所以我要将其更改为7.5
i'm going to hit tab to skip over to the
我要按Tab键跳到
height and change that to 10
高度并将其更改为10
and then press enter and it should now
然后按Enter键，它现在应该
be an inch smaller now what we have to
现在我们要做的就是缩小一英寸
do is center this
做的就是把这个放在中心
up on the page so where it says relative
在页面上，上面写着相对
to change this to page over here in the
要将其更改为PAGE，请在
align distribute menu
对齐分布菜单
and we're looking for center on vertical
我们正在寻找垂直方向的中心
axis and center on horizontal axis
轴和水平轴上的中心
and this right here is going to define
而这将在这里定义
where the contents of the page
其中，页面的内容
are we don't want to leave this red
我们是不是不想让这一切变成红色
object sitting here though so we're
坐在这里的物体，所以我们
going to convert this to guides
要将其转换为辅助线
come up here to where it says object and
到这里来，上面写着反对和
go to
去
convert objects to guides and now we
将对象转换为辅助线，现在我们
have guides there to reference as we're
有指南可供参考，因为我们
creating our design
创造我们的设计
so the first thing we're going to do to
所以我们要做的第一件事是
create the design that i showed you in
创建我在中向您展示的设计
the beginning of the video is we're
这段视频的开头是我们
going to create some
我要创建一些
header text or title text up here let me
标题文本或标题文本在这里让我
grab the
抓起
text tool let me click and drag actually
文本工具实际上让我点击并拖动
i'm going to snap to the corner of these
我要抓住这些的一角
these guides over here and then just
这些导游在这里，然后
click and drag to create a title area
单击并拖动以创建标题区域
i'm just going to title this monthly
我只想给这本月刊起个标题
report
报告
and i'm going to change this make this
我要改变这一切，让这一切
bold
大胆
maybe make this a smaller size go with
也许可以把这件小一点的搭配一下
something like 20
大概20岁左右
and if you want to change the font you
如果您想更改字体，请
can do so over here i'm going to leave
可以在这里做，我要走了
the default sans font
默认的SANS字体
for now leave that now i want to put a
现在离开，现在我想把一个
page
页面
number over here so let me just
号码在这里，所以让我
duplicate this text object i'll right
复制此文本对象我就对了
click it go to duplicate
单击它转到复制
and i'll change this let me grab the
我要换掉这个，让我拿一下
text tool change this to zero
文本工具将其更改为零
one because this will be page one and
一是因为这将是第一页
let me uh
让我来吧
let me make this a little smaller first
让我先把这个弄小一点
of all i wanna remove the bold i'm gonna
最重要的是，我想去掉那些大胆的
make this normal
让这一切变得正常
and then i'll just make this maybe
然后我会把这件事
something like 16
大概16岁左右
that looks pretty good and now we can
这看起来很好，现在我们可以
just place this in the top right corner
把这个放在右上角
over here
在这里
i'm going to zoom in on this to zoom in
我要放大这个来放大
i'm just holding ctrl and rolling up the
我只是按住Ctrl键并卷起
mouse wheel to move the page just press
只需按鼠标滚轮即可移动页面
down the mouse wheel and move the mouse
向下移动鼠标滚轮并移动鼠标
i just want to manually place this in
我只想手动将它放入
the corner here unfortunately these text
不幸的是，这里的角落里有这些文字
objects will not snap into
对象不会捕捉到
your guides unless it's the base of the
你的向导，除非它是
text object like you see here but
文本对象，如您在这里看到的，但是
that's not what we're looking for so
这不是我们要找的，所以
we're going to leave that right there as
我们将把它留在那里，因为
it is let me zoom back out
它让我把它放大
and now i just want to create like a
现在我只想创造一个
little divider to put right here so i'm
把小隔板放在这里，所以我
going to grab the rectangle tool again
再次抓取矩形工具
click and drag to create like a little
单击并拖动以创建类似于
rectangle going from one side to the
矩形从一边到另一边
other
其他
that's looking pretty good i'll make
看起来很不错，我会做的
this something like yellow
这是黄色的吗？
grab the select tool move this up like
抓起选择工具，像这样向上移动
that
那
let me zoom in so i can get a little
让我放大一点，这样我就可以
closer there we go that's what i'm
我们走得更近，这就是我要做的
looking for
寻找
and i want to make a copy of this
我想把这个复制一份
divider and put it at the bottom of the
分隔符并将其放在
page too so let me right click this and
页面也是如此，所以让我右击此页
go to duplicate
转到复制
and i will put this divider at the
我会把这个分隔线放在
bottom of the page where the bottom of
页面的底部，其中
the margin is
保证金是
and now i want to create some content
现在我想创建一些内容
area for our design here
我们的设计区在这里
what i'm going to do for this particular
我要为这个特别的节目做些什么
design i'm going to create two columns
设计我将创建两个专栏
of text
文本的
if you want you could just use one giant
如果你想，你可以只用一个巨型的
block of text i'm going to put a little
一段文字，我要放一小段
more design into this so i'm going to
更多的设计，所以我要
use two columns of text here so
在这里使用两列文本，以便
let me grab the rectangle tool again let
让我再次抓起矩形工具，让
me create another rectangle going
我要创建另一个矩形
through the uh
通过这个
through the uh guidelines here and let
通过这里的指南，让我们
me just make this red let me bring down
我只要把这个做成红色，让我把它拿下来
the opacity
不透明
and i want to divide this up into two
我想把这个一分为二
separate evenly sized and evenly spaced
大小均匀、间距均匀的独立部件
apart
分开
rectangle so to do that i'm going to
矩形，所以为了做到这一点，我要
create another rectangle going through
创建另一个穿过的矩形
the center here
这里的中心
like this and i'm going to center that
像这样，我要把那个放在中间
up on the page
在页面上
grab the select tool hold shift
抓住选择工具按住Shift键
click on the object there and go to path
单击那里的对象并转到路径
difference so those are now two
不同的是，现在是两个
different objects and i'm just going to
不同的物体，我只是要
zoom in i'm going to hold ctrl roll up
放大我要按住Ctrl键向上滚动
the mouse wheel to zoom in a little bit
鼠标滚轮可以稍微放大一点
position this down here a little further
把这个放在这里再往下一点
we don't want this
我们不想这样
we don't want this flush against the
我们不想让这场比赛与
guide here because the text is going to
这里是指南，因为文本将
be in this red area we don't want the
在这个红色区域，我们不想要
text to be stacked on top of this
要堆叠在此顶部的文本
divider so
分隔符SO
a little bit of padding in there should
在里面加一点填充物应该会
help something like that looks pretty
帮个忙，这样的东西看起来很漂亮
good
好的
and i don't want these text columns to
我不想让这些文本栏
be this high so i'm just going to take
要这么高，所以我要把
this top arrow and just bring this down
这个向上的箭头，然后把这个放下来
i'm going to leave these two text
我要留下这两条短信
columns right
列向右
here and i'm going to put some other
在这里，我要放一些其他的
contents up here
这里有一些东西
which we will go over momentarily so let
我们会马上讲一遍，所以让我们
me zoom in
我放大
let's break this apart into two separate
让我们把它分成两个独立的
objects we'll go to path
我们将转到路径的对象
break apart and now we'll go to
分开，现在我们要去
objects object to guides
对象对象到辅助线
and we now just created guides that we
我们现在刚刚创建了指南，我们
can reference for placing our text
可以为放置我们的文本提供参考
so let's go ahead and place some
所以让我们继续放一些
placeholder text in here i'm just going
这里的占位符文本我只是要
to copy and paste
复制和粘贴
some lorem ipsum dummy text
一些lorem ipsum虚拟文本
and let me grab the text tool over here
让我拿一下这里的文本工具
click and drag this corner
单击并拖动此角
down to here like that i'm just going to
就这样走到这里，我只是要
hit ctrl
按Ctrl键
v to paste my text in there now this is
将我的文本粘贴到这里，这是
a little too big let me
有点太大了，让我来
let me select all of this and ctrl a to
让我选择所有这些并按Ctrl a键
select all
选择所有
i want to bring the size down to like
我想把尺码降到像
maybe 12.
也许是12个。
i'm just going to go ahead and add some
我只想继续添加一些
more text in here now let me just copy
这里有更多的文字，现在让我来复制
and paste more of this alarm if some
并粘贴更多的此警报，如果一些
text now if you notice
如果你注意到了，现在就发短信
if you if your text is too long it's
如果你如果你的短信太长了
going to run to the end of the page here
我将在这里运行到页面末尾
so let me take this little node and just
所以让我用这个小节点
drag this down
把这个往下拖
and as you can see the text is running
如您所见，文本正在运行
through the edge here so if
穿过这里的边缘，所以如果
your text is bleeding out to the edge
你的文字快流血到边缘了
just go ahead and select it and delete
只需继续选择并删除即可
it
它
and you'll have to continue it on in
你将不得不继续它在
this column over here this is one of the
这里的这一栏这是
reasons why i think inkscape probably
我认为Inkscape可能
isn't the best tool for this sort of
不是这种情况下最好的工具
thing because
因为这件事
you got to do a lot of manual copy and
你得做大量的手工复印
pasting with the text
与文本一起粘贴
if you want if you notice the text here
如果您愿意，如果您注意到这里的文字
we have this spacing on the right side
我们在右边有这个间隔
if you want to make it so that the text
如果你想让它成为文本
runs to the to the edges of both sides
延伸到两边的边缘
uh what you can do is you can come up to
呃你能做的就是你能达到
the uh justification up here
呃，这里的理由是
the alignment rather and then change to
而是对齐，然后更改为
change it to this option right here and
在此处将其更改为此选项，然后
if you notice it spaces the text out so
如果您注意到它将文本隔开，那么
it runs to the edges like that
它就像那样跑到了边缘
i don't like how that looks personally
我个人不喜欢这件事的样子
it looks too like robotic so i'm just
它看起来太像机器人了，所以我只是
gonna
会不会
leave it as it was before and then we're
让它保持原来的样子，然后我们就
gonna do the same thing over here create
我会在这里做同样的事情来创建
some more text i'm gonna make this box
更多的文字，我要制作这个方框
even bigger this time so i don't have to
这次更大了，这样我就不用
change the size of it and again we're
改变它的大小，我们又一次
just gonna uh
只是要呃
i'm just gonna control paste use this
我要用这个控制浆糊
dummy text here
此处为虚拟文本
let me select all control a to select
让我选择所有要选择的控件a
all change the size of this to match the
全部更改此对象的大小以匹配
size of the other text i'm gonna use 12.
我将使用的其他文本的大小为12。
and for this one i'm going to maybe
对于这一次，我可能会
shorten this
缩短这段时间
by about this much because for this
差不多是这么多，因为
design i'm going to use
我要用到的设计
like a placeholder graphic over here
就像这里的占位符图形
like a chart or some kind of
就像一张图表或某种
pie chart or something like that go back
饼图或类似的东西回到过去
to the select tool
添加到选择工具
okay so now that part is done what we
好的，现在这部分已经完成了，我们
could do now is create like a text area
现在可以做的是创建一个类似于文本区域的
in here like a like a header section
在这里就像一个页眉部分
to do that i'm going to grab the white
为了做到这一点，我要抓住白色的
rectangle that represents the page
表示页面的矩形
i'm going to right click that and go to
我要右键单击它，然后转到
duplicate and i'm just going to take
复制件，我要把它
this bottom arrow and scale it up like
这个下箭头，然后按如下方式放大
this
这
bring it up to about there let me change
把它拿到那里，让我换一件
the color of this so we can see what
这个的颜色，这样我们就能看到
we're doing here i'm going to make this
我们在这里做，我要做这件事
like a dark shade of blue like that
就像深蓝色那样
you can use whatever color you like i'll
你可以用你喜欢的任何颜色，我会
take this top arrow bring this down
拿上这个箭头，把这个放下来
and we're going to use this area right
我们将正确使用这片区域
here to add some like uh
在这里添加一些像这样的
leader text or header text and before i
引线文本或页眉文本和I之前
do that though i just want to make sure
尽管我只是想确保
that this is evenly spaced out between
它们之间的距离是均匀的
this text object
此文本对象
this blue rectangle and this yellow
这个蓝色的矩形和这个黄色的
divider i want to make sure all three of
分隔器我想确保这三个人
these are evenly spaced out so i'm going
这些都是均匀分布的，所以我要
to click on the divider
要单击分隔线，请执行以下操作
hold shift click on the blue box hold
按住Shift键单击蓝色框中的按住键
shift
换班
click on the text and come over here to
点击文本，然后来到这里
where it says distribute
上面写着分发
and we're looking for this icon down
我们正在寻找这个图标
here towards the bottom right that says
在右下角，上面写着
make vertical gaps between objects equal
使对象之间的垂直间距相等
go ahead and click on that
继续并点击该按钮
and there we go so let me uh create some
我们开始了，所以让我，呃，创造一些
text to put in here i'm going to grab
要放在这里的文本我要抓取
the text tool
文本工具
snap to the left guide right here
在此处捕捉到左侧辅助线
put that right there i'm just going to
把它放在那里，我要去
use header text
使用页眉文本
i'm going to make that white
我要把它变成白色
and maybe i'll make that a little bigger
也许我会把它弄大一点
maybe something like 30 32 that should
也许应该是30-32左右。
be pretty good
做得很好
and now i want to use this divider for
现在我想用这个分隔器来
this design i'm going to use this
这个设计我要用这个
divider down here as well so let me take
隔板也在这里，所以让我来吧
that divider
那个分隔符
duplicate that by right clicking it
通过右键单击来复制它
going to duplicate
要复制
put this over here and i want this
把这个放在这里，我想要这个
divider to be the same width of this
分隔符的宽度与此相同
text so let me click on the text
文本，让我点击文本
right click it and go to copy and then
右键单击它并转到复制，然后
click on the divider and go to edit
单击分隔线并转到编辑
paste size paste with
粘贴大小粘贴方式
and then i can go ahead and paste this
然后我可以继续粘贴这个
move this over here like that
把这个像那样搬到这里来
i'm going to zoom in so that the snaps
我要放大，这样这些快照
won't get in the way there we go
不会挡住我们去的路
and now i'm going to put some subtext
现在我要把一些潜台词
down here so let me click on this
在这里，让我点击这个
right click it duplicate put this down
用鼠标右键点击复制将其放下
here
这里
make this white grab the text tool again
让这个白色再次抓取文本工具
and uh sub
还有，呃，潜艇
text can go here
可在此处查看文本
let me just stack this next to it like
让我把这个放在它旁边，就像
that
那
now it's looking pretty good let me zoom
现在它看起来很好，让我放大
in just make sure these are
只要确保这些是
evenly spaced apart looking pretty good
均匀分布的看起来很不错
now i'm going to put some text in here
现在我要在这里输入一些文本
on this right side to do that
在这右边做这件事
let me grab the text tool i'm going to
让我拿起我要去的文本工具
start over here on this guideline
从这里开始遵循这条指导方针
click and drag like this let me try that
像这样点击并拖动，让我试试那个
again i'm going to click and drag to
我将再次单击并拖动到
create this text box
创建此文本框
ctrl v to paste there we go make that
Ctrl v粘贴到那里我们去做那个
white
白色
uh ctrl a to select it all i'm going to
呃Ctrl a来选择它，我要去
make this one slightly bigger than this
把这个做得比这个大一点
body text over here so this was size to
正文文本在这里，所以这是大小
12. i'm going to size this at maybe uh
12.我打算把这件衣服的尺寸改成呃
16 see how that looks
16看看那是什么样子
that looks pretty good i'm going to go
看起来很不错，我要走了。
ahead and remove some of this that we
去掉一些我们认为
don't have so much of that in there
别放那么多东西在里面
okay looking pretty good now if you're
好的，现在看起来很不错，如果你
not happy with the width of this text
对这篇文章的宽度不满意
what you can do is let me zoom in a
你能做的就是让我放大一个
little bit
一点点
you can move this over like this
你可以像这样把这个移过去
and then you can go back to the text
然后你可以回到课文
tool and take this node right here and
工具，将这个节点放在这里，然后
just snap it to the right side so that
只需把它扣到右边，这样就可以
it changes the uh the orientation of it
它改变了它的方向
like that
就像这样
now let me grab the select tool i want
现在让我抓起我想要的选择工具
to center this text up within this blue
要将此文本居中放置在此蓝色中
object so i'm going to hold shift and
反对，所以我要按住Shift键并
click on the blue text i mean the blue
点击蓝色文本我是指蓝色
object
对象
and i'm going to change the relative to
我要将相对关系更改为
i'm going to change that to last
我要把它改成持久的
selected
已选择
and i'm going to center it up on the
我将把它集中在
horizontal axis like that
像这样的水平轴
and now i want this text to to be
现在我希望这篇文章是
aligned to the top of this
与此顶部对齐
text so let me click and drag over those
文本，这样我就可以点击并拖动这些文本
three objects right there to select them
就在那里的三个对象来选择它们
or what you could do is you could just
或者你可以做的是，你可以
click them one by one while holding
按住按钮的同时逐个点击
shift
换班
and then just group them together with
然后将它们组合在一起
this button that says group selected
此按钮表示已选择组
objects
对象
or you can just press ctrl g hold shift
或者您也可以只按ctrl g按住Shift键
click on this text right here and then
点击此处，然后点击此文本
just where it says uh align top edges
就在它说，呃，对齐顶部边缘的地方
click on that and that right there is
点击它，它就在那里
what we're looking for so let me zoom
我们要找的东西，让我放大
out a little bit
有点出局了
let me click off of this to deselect
让我单击此选项以取消选择
everything now what you could do now is
现在你能做的一切就是
you can import an image in here if you
在以下情况下，您可以在此处导入图像
want to do what i did if you want to
想做我做过的事吗？如果你想的话
add some more flair to this design what
给这个设计增添一些新元素什么
i'm going to do is i'm going to
我要做的是我要
import my image over here i have it
把我的图像输入到这里我有它
opened up on my other monitor if i can
如果可以，在我的另一台显示器上打开
just find it we go
只要找到它，我们就走
i'll bring my folder this is the folder
我会带上我的文件夹，这是我的文件夹
right here
就在这里
i'll bring it into the screen if you
我会把它放到屏幕上，如果你
just take your image and just click and
只需获取您的图像并点击即可
drag it onto inkscape like that
像这样拖到Inkscape上
leave the defaults as it is click ok and
保留默认设置不变，然后单击确定
there's my image
这是我的形象
i just want to send this to the bottom
我只想把这个送到谷底
of the image i'm going to right click
我要右击的图像
this
这
actually no i'm going to come over here
实际上，不，我要过来。
to where it says lower selection to the
设置为将选项设置为较低
bottom
底部
click on that and then i want to raise
点击这一点，然后我想提出
that one step so it's above
这一步，所以它在上面
the white page so i'm going to click
白页，所以我要点击
this button over here that says raise
这里的这个按钮上写着举起
selection
选择
one step and if at any point you want to
一步，如果你想在任何时候
see how your design is looking without
查看您的设计在没有
these guides in the way you could just
这些指南就像你可以
come over here where it says view
到这里来，上面写着风景
and then deselect guides what i like to
然后取消选择我喜欢的指南
do is use the keyboard shortcut which is
所做的就是使用键盘快捷键
this
这
vertical line right here so i'm going to
竖线就在这里，所以我要
toggle them off and on to see how they
关闭和打开它们，以查看它们如何
look
看
okay so let me center this up on the
好的，让我把这个集中在
blue box right here let me select that
这里的蓝色方框让我来选择
hold shift click on the blue box
按住Shift键并单击蓝色框
center it up vertically and horizontally
垂直居中和水平居中
like that click off of it to deselect
就像点击它来取消选择
everything
所有的一切
take just this blue box and bring the
只拿这个蓝色的盒子，带上
opacity down a little bit so
不透明度降低一点，所以
the image shows beneath it then i want
图像显示在它的下面，然后我想
to take this image
拍下这张照片
hold ctrl and shift and scale it down
按住Ctrl键和Shift键并将其缩小
like that
就像这样
that's pretty good let me zoom in move
这很好，让我放大移动。
this up
这个就起来了
okay so now i just want to crop this
好的，现在我只想剪掉这个
image so that it fits this blue square
图像，以便它适合这个蓝色正方形
right here so let me take the blue
就在这里，让我来拿蓝色的
square
正方形
right click it go to duplicate hold
右键单击它，转到复制暂挂
shift
换班
click on the image and go to object clip
单击图像并转到对象剪辑
object clip set and there we go
对象剪辑设置，然后开始
now let me take this and just adjust the
现在让我拿着这个，调整一下
opacity so that some of it shows through
不透明，因此其中一些可以透过
that right there looks pretty good
就在那里，看起来很不错
now let me zoom out i'm going to come
现在让我把镜头拉远，我要来了
over here now to where it says view let
现在到这里来，上面写着让我们观看
me toggle off the guide so we can see
我把导游关掉，这样我们就能看到
how it looks
它看起来怎么样
and as you can see our design is looking
如你所见，我们的设计看起来
pretty good now you can use this area
很好，现在你可以使用这个区域了
here to import like an infographic or a
此处导入的内容类似于信息图或
pie chart or something like i did i'm
像我这样的饼状图之类的东西
going to leave it blank for now
暂时将其留空
as it stands this design is looking like
就目前而言，这个设计看起来像是
it's finished so what i'm going to do is
它已经完成了，所以我要做的是
i'm going to save it as a pdf document
我要把它另存为pdf文档
i'll go to file
我会去归档的
save as i'm just going to title this
保留，因为我将给这本书命名
thing
一件事
report and for the file
报告和文件
save save as type i'm going to change
我要更改另存为类型
that to pdf
转到pdf
right there there we go and i'll go
就在那里，我们走，我会走的
ahead and save
超前和节省
you leave the defaults as they are go
您保留默认设置不变
ahead and click ok
前进，然后点击确定
ok now the downside of one of the other
好的，现在其中一个的缺点是
downsides of doing this with inkscape is
使用Inkscape执行此操作的缺点是
that you'll have to design
必须由你来设计
your report or your book one page at a
你的报告或你的书一页一页
time
时间
and then save all of the individual
然后拯救所有的个体
pages as individual pdfs
页面作为单独的pdf
and then use something like pdf sam to
然后使用像pdf Sam这样的东西来
merge the pdf document together i'll
将pdf文档合并在一起，我将
show you that in just a minute
稍等片刻，给你展示一下
again this is one of the downsides of
再说一次，这是
using inkscape that's why i recommend if
使用Inkscape，这就是为什么我推荐
you're creating something really long
你在创造一个很长的东西
like a 50 or 60 page book
就像一本50或60页的书
probably not a good idea to use inkscape
使用Inkscape可能不是一个好主意
but if you just want to create a one or
但如果您只是想创建一个或
two page report like this
像这样的两页报告
that's fine so let me um let me uh
很好，那么让我，
minimize this now let me come back over
现在最小化，让我再来一次
here to my folder i'm looking for
这里是我要找的文件夹
report.pdf what i'm going to do is we're
Pdf我要做的是我们
going to save a second copy of this
我要保存此文件的第二份副本
file save as i'm going to save a second
文件保存，因为我要保存一秒钟
a second copy of this just so i can
再复印一份这样我就可以
demonstrate how this works
演示此功能的工作原理
report to
报告对象
pdf click save
PDF点击保存
so now what i've done here is i opened
所以现在我在这里做的是我打开了
up a piece of software known as pdf sam
安装了一款名为pdf Sam的软件
this is a free piece of software i'll
这是一款免费的软件，我会
have a link in the description if you
在描述中有链接，如果您
want to download it this just allows you
想要下载它，这只会让你
to merge pdf documents together pretty
要将pdf文档合并在一起非常漂亮
quickly
速战速决
if you want you can use a web-based
如果您愿意，您可以使用基于Web的
solution if you'd like you don't have to
解决方案，如果您愿意，您不必这样做
download software to do this
下载软件即可完成此操作
come over here to where it says merge
到这里来，上面写着合并
and i'm going to take these two
我要把这两个人
documents and place them in here like
文件，然后放在这里，就像
this and it's going to ask you where you
它会问你在哪里
want to place this i'm going to place it
想把这个放进去我就把它放进去
where it originally was
它最初所在的地方
and i'm going to leave everything as it
我要让一切都像它一样
is and click run
是并单击运行
and there we go so let me open up this
就这样，让我打开这个
document
文件
and as you can see here we have a
正如您在这里看到的，我们有一个
two-page pdf document that we created
我们创建的两页pdf文档
with inkscape and you can take this text
使用inkscape，您可以使用此文本
and highlight it and copy and paste it
并突出显示并复制粘贴
just like you would with any other pdf
就像使用任何其他pdf一样
document
文件
and the great thing about this again is
这件事的伟大之处在于
since we created this in inkscape this
自从我们在水墨景观中创建了这个以来，
is a vector
是矢量
design meaning you can zoom in on this
设计意味着您可以放大它
and you won't get that pixelization you
而且你不会得到像素化
get that
得到那个
the benefit of working with vectors like
使用诸如此类的载体的好处
that so i think that should do it for
所以我认为这应该就够了
this tutorial that's how you can go
这个教程就是你可以如何去
about using inkscape
关于使用inkscape
for some pretty rudimentary desktop
对于一些相当初级的桌面
publishing purposes
出版目的
if you have any questions just leave a
如果您有任何问题，请留下一个
comment below and as always thanks for
下面评论，一如既往地感谢
[Music]
[音乐]
watching
看